

## Krisztina Kovari

Junior Web Developer

krystonen@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/krystonen/ github.com/krystonen krisztinakovari.com

> Nederlands: NTT2 B1 +(31)-652-343-703

#### Profile

Junior full-stack web developer excited to build a career in technology focusing on Javascript, CSS and JS front-end frameworks. I come from a Digital Media background and I turned towards software development to expand my horizons and to maximise the qualities that drove me in my previous job experiences: working with the latest technologies, a problem solving mindset, the desire for personal growth and room for creativity. I am hard-working and as passionate about coding as about learning.

# Software Projects

**Portfolio Website** https://github.com/krystonen/portfolio February 2019

- A portfolio website built in Ruby on Rails 5.2 that showcases Rails best practices (helpers, concerns, partials, forms with nested attributes) and a lot of advanced features: Drag&Drop portfolio items, Streaming live data for blog comments, Multiple layouts, Twitter API integration, Session Data Usage, Ruby Gem Creation, Authentication, Authorisation etc.
- ► Technologies used: Ruby on Rails, SQL, Javascript, ActionCable, API, AWS, Bootstrap 4, HTML, SCSS, CSS, jQuery, CoffeeScript

Submaster http://www.submaster.club/

November 2018

- A mobile-sized web site I created in 2 weeks at the Le Wagon bootcamp with a team of 4
  aspiring developers. The website aims to help teachers to find substitute teachers in their
  field easily. A teacher can submit a class for substitution or take a class to teach, check
  statuses on dashboard, get in touch with other teachers etc.
- ▶ Technologies used: Figma, DB Design, Ruby on Rails, SQL, Bootstrap, SCSS, HTML, Heroku, Git, Github

Promo Campaign https://promo-campaign.herokuapp.com/

March 2019

- A simple webpage to showcase user input validation with React & Javascript in Rails.
- ▶ Technologies used: React, Javascript, Ruby on Rails, Webpack, SCSS, HTML

### Employment History

#### Video On Demand Supervisor at Viacom, Amsterdam

June 2016 — January 2018

- Increased quantity and quality of content delivery (Amazon, iTunes, Ziggo, Singtel, iFlix etc).
- Increased content distribution by managing technical on-boarding of clients and by keeping documentation up-to-date.
- Successfully planned and migrated workflows on system upgrades.
- Managed artwork production following style guides for global content distribution.

#### **Video On Demand Supervisor at AMC Networks, Amsterdam** (now TVT)

April 2013 — May 2016

- Contributed to development processes by translating demands into actionable projects.
- Conducted error management and troubleshooting (JIRA)
- Ensured smooth technical on-boarding of new clients (XSLT creation, testing).
- Analysed trends and made adjustments in business rules based on monthly reports.

#### Scheduling Supervisor | Scheduler, at DMC, Amsterdam (now TVT)

February 2008 — April 2013

- Ensured that daily transmission schedules were planned in a timely and reliable manner.
- Contributed to company's growth by providing successful trainings on scheduling systems.

#### Education

#### Full Stack Web Developer at Le Wagon, Amsterdam

September 2018 – November 2018

Le Wagon is a product-driven program teaching the core concepts of programming and web development. During the course I practiced building web applications, collaborated within a team of developers and adopted the technical workflows followed by successful startups.

# Master of Hungarian Language and Literature, at Eötvös Loránd University, Budapest

September 1996 - June 2001

I studied to become a teacher in Budapest. Although I never practiced as a teacher, in all my professions I aim to be a clear communicator and I put a lot of emphasis on sharing knowledge. Besides my major, I also studied English and participated in a pioneering program at the time called "Humanities Informatics".